cocoacontrols.com 2015-03-20

# Privacy Policy - Cocoa Controls

Receive our weekly roundup before it gets posted on the site! 

## Legal Information

Cocoa Controls (which means here Cocoa Controls at Red Gate Software Limited) respects your privacy. We do not sell, rent or loan any identifiable information regarding our customers to any third party. Any information you give us is held with the utmost care and security.

This privacy policy sets out our privacy practices. Please take time to review this privacy policy as it tells you how your personal information will be treated by us.

Any questions regarding our privacy policy should be directed at info@cocoacontrols.com.

## Use of information

Cocoa Controls will not collect any personal information about individuals except when specifically and knowingly provided by such individuals. Examples of such information are: name, company, postal address, email address, phone number and product commentary.

We will use the personal information provided to us in order to:

  * process orders submitted by you;
  * customize the service we provide to you;
  * administrate or otherwise carry out our obligations in relation to any agreement you have with us;
  * verify your identity (for example if you participate in any promotions administered by us);
  * anticipate and resolve any problems with any goods or services supplied to you;
  * carry out market research and surveys and track sales data;
  * send you our newsletter, where this is requested by you;
  * to send you follow-up communications relating to software downloaded from our site; and
  * send you information about our other products and services.

We may collect any personal information provided by you to us through this website or via one of our telephone operators, or we may collect this information through your email or other communications with us. Certain information is collected automatically, as described later in the privacy policy.

We may also ask you for other optional information such as what sort of equipment/device/software you use and what other subjects interest you. If you choose to give us this information, we will use it to help us to provide you with the best possible service that is personalized to your needs and preferences.

Although we do not make it compulsory to give us every item of information we ask for, the more information you volunteer (and the more accurate it is), the better we can tailor our services for you.

We also collect information from you if you choose to take part in any of our on-site surveys or promotions. We will use this information to administer the promotion and help us to plan other promotions.

Certain Cocoa Controls, such as payment processing, are offered in conjunction with our business partners. In such cases, we may need to share your personal information with them in order to provide these services. Please note that certain services may be unavailable if you do not want to disclose the personal information you are asked for.

## Log files/IP addresses

When you visit our site, we automatically log your IP address which is recognized by our web server. We use IP addresses to help us administer the site and to collect broad demographic information for aggregate use.

Non personal information 

We may automatically collect non-personal information about you, such as the type of internet browsers you use or the site from which you linked to our site. You cannot be identified from this information and it is only used to assist us in providing an effective service on our site.

Cocoa Controls may share non-personal aggregate or summary information regarding its customers with partners or other third parties, such as information relating to the number of users linking to our site from their sites but Cocoa Controls does not sell or share any information at the individual level.

## Cookies

Cookies are very small text files saved to your computer used to track user navigation around a website. On Cocoa Controls session cookies are used when users log-in to the site. Cocoa Controls will use such cookies to identify unique users to our sites. They are not cross-referenced with any other information such that an individual person could be identified.

Cocoa Controls may use a third party to serve advertisements on our sites. The advertisers may use cookies to track the number of users responding to the campaign. Cocoa Controls does not have access to or control of cookies placed by third parties.

Disabling/Enabling Cookies - users have the ability to accept or disable cookies by modifying the settings in their browser. Disabling cookies, however, may mean that some functionality may be affected. For further directions on how to disable cookies please visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/stop-cookies-installed.html

## Disclosures

Other than the disclosures referred to in this policy, we will not disclose any personal information without your permission unless we are legally obliged or entitled to do so (for example, if required to do so by Court order or for the purposes of fraud or other crime).

We will only disclose your personal information to a third party either as part of a reorganization or a sale of the assets of Red Gate Software, or having ensured that steps have been taken to ensure that your privacy rights continue to be protected.

## Information about products and services

It is very important to us that we provide you with the highest level of service. In order to help us do this, from time to time Cocoa Controls may send you, with your consent, details of our products and services which we think may be of interest to you. If at any time you do not wish to continue to receive these details, then send an email message to info@cocoacontrol.com with “unsubscribe from Cocoa Controls”

## Keeping our records accurate

We aim to keep our information about you as accurate as possible. If you would like to review or change the details you have supplied us with, please contact us as set out below.

## User discussion forums

Cocoa Controls may make chat rooms, forums, message boards and/or other news groups available to its users. Any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should always be careful when deciding to disclose your personal information.

## Security

We have implemented technology and policies to help safeguard your privacy from unauthorized access and improper use. For example, transactions conducted through the site are encrypted and user log-in is subject to password protection. We will continue to monitor and update security measures as new technology becomes available as appropriate to the site.

## Third party sites

We cannot be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of other sites even if you access them using links from our site and recommend that you check the policy of each site you visit.

In addition, if you linked to our site from a third party site, we cannot be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of the owners or operators of that third party site and recommend that you check the policy of that third party site and contact its owner or operator if you have any concerns or questions.

## Transfers of your personal information outside of the European Economic Area

Information you provide to us is not routinely transferred by us to countries outside the European Economic Area (EEA) although it may happen if at any point one of our servers is temporarily located in a country outside the EEA or if one of our service providers is located in a country outside of the EEA. If we transfer your information outside the EEA in this way, we will take steps to ensure that your privacy rights continue to be protected.

In addition, if you use our services while you are outside the EEA, your information will be transferred outside the EEA in order to provide you with those services.

## Your consent

By using our website, or giving us your details at an exhibition, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Cocoa Controls. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we would disclose it.

## Contacting us

If at any time you would like to contact us with your views about our privacy practices, or with any enquiry relating to your personal information, you can do so by sending an email to us at info@cocoacontrols.com or by contacting us at Cocoa Controls, Red Gate Software Limited, Newnham House, Cambridge Business Park, Cambridge, CB4 0WZ, United Kingdom. You are entitled to ask for a copy of the information we store about you (for which we may charge a small fee).

×

### Is this hosted on GitHub?

If this control is hosted on GitHub, paste the address below, otherwise click "Not Hosted on GitHub".
